shopr.com 2012-12-05

# Shopr.com

##### Privacy Policy

Effective **February 13, 2009**  
**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**

  * Our Commitment To Privacy
  * The Information We Collect
  * How We Use Information
  * Our Commitment To Data Security
  * How To Access Or Correct Your Information
  * How To Contact Us

**Our Commitment To Privacy**

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Shopr website. On some pages, you can make requests or recommendations, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

  * Name
  * Email address
  * Gender
  * Age

There are frequent links leading to pages outside the control of Shopr. On these pages, our privacy policies are superceded by those of the page upon which you land.

On some pages, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you invite another user to join the site, via a recommendation, project or direct invitation, you will need to submit the recipient's email address. In this circumstance, the email address is all that is collected.

**The Way We Use Information:**

We use the information you provide about yourself when performing price comparison operations. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the price comparison request.

We use the information you provide about someone else only to send an invitation email. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete the invitation.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. 

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain via the Profile page. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error (or change it yourself via the Profile page).

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us**

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [info@shopr.com](mailto:info@shopr.com).

This policy was adapted from a template provided by the [Better Business Bureau](http://www.bbbonline.org/Privacy/sample_privacy.asp).
